

- ohheycerimay@gmail.com
- ohheycerimay.com
- Cleveland, OH willing to relocate

SKILLS

- · Problem-solving
- Ability to collaborate effectively
- Object Oriented Programming
- Debugging and Troubleshooting
- Communication
- Database Management
- Continuous Learning

LANGUAGES & FRAMEWORKS

- React.js
- Javascript
- Ruby
- Ruby on Rails
- Python
- CSS
- HTML

CERI MAY DORSEY-TYLER

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

A highly motivated and enthusiastic software engineer with a passion for problem-solving and creating efficient solutions, my journey in technology started while working as a bartender where I developed a strong customer-focused mindset and a keen eye for detail for over a decade. I am now eager to bring my customer-focused approach, drive for excellence, and technical abilities to a company where I can continue to grow and make an impact.

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

Yes Chef | Github

- With its intuitive interface, the app makes it easy to add, update, and remove items from the inventory.
- Issued the functionality for users to see when their stock was running low, and resupply when needed.

Wander | Github

- Set up authorization and authentication for users to log in, log out and sign up.
- Paired programming project developed with React.js and Ruby on Rails

GoT or Not | Github

- Established a unique page with React.js through fun ideas and creative CSS
- Provided users with the full "dating app" experience by adding their profile, and delete characters by "swiping right".

WORK EXPERIENCE

Live Nation | Bartender

March 2023 - Present

- handled multiple tasks at once, such as making drinks, taking orders, and handling payments.
- interacted with customers in a friendly and professional manner while building customer loyalty and ensuring a positive experience for guests.

Le Fanfare | Bartender

June 2018 - April 2020

- worked as part of a team and able to collaborate and communicate effectively with other staff members.
- kept a strong work ethic in a fast paced environment.

EDUCATION

Flatiron School | 2022-2023

Full Stack Web Development, Ruby on Rails and JavaScript program